I can see you in love, you live
I can feel you in love, you live
This温もり is where to go
If we are tomorrow, we will die
If we are in love, we will die
We will die
I can feel you in love, I can feel you in love
I can feel you in love
See you next time.
That was a close call, but we made it.
Goodbye. I thought you weren't supposed to use your magic.
Hmm. I doubt it will cause any trouble.
That was technically a different kind of magic than I've used in the past.
This type of magic uses sound. Its basis is much different than the kind I specialize in.
You wouldn't have had to do that if I'd come up with a better escape plan in the first place. I'm really sorry.
Don't worry about it. You did the best you could, right? Besides, it was worth it. You recovered one of Sakura's feathers.
I know the watchdogs that were set to guard the library attacked us, but I don't remember anything after that.
But I can still feel it in my legs. The echo of a memory. The tingling that comes after I defeat someone.
What's wrong? Is that injury you got still hurting you?
No, it's not so bad.
Are you sure?
They always find trouble.
Let's see.
What kind of world are we in this time?
Wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up.
Who said that?
Wake up, wake up, wake up.
Not exactly welcoming, is it?
What's up, Sharon?
These edges.
They've all been rounded off by something.
Yeah, what does that matter?
They're completely smooth.
I don't think normal erosion would do this.
Ow!
This is weird rain. It hurts.
It does burn.
It looks like that building over there is still intact.
Come on!
Mummy!
Almost there.
We should be safe once we reach it.
I'm glad to be out of that.
Much longer and we'd be full of holes.
We're safe!
Not quite.
Take a look behind you.
I'm going to take a look around in there.
All right, be careful.
Oh, no.
Poor Sakura.
I'm glad you're not awake to see this.
Okina I have to look for the better I can't hide in there so brave can't you sense anything here yet
I'm not sure I feel something very powerful but I don't know what it is where's it coming from
do you know the penalty for trespassing here I hope you're ready to die I haven't seen this one
before me neither but that kick was cool don't start admiring his moves he's trespassing and most
likely a thief so what do we do with him come away interesting your game
you can't wait five minutes before getting yourself in trouble huh hey thanks cream puff hand over my
sword would you you guys made the first move just remember that I take it you're the boss man right
arrogant isn't he does he actually think he can beat Kamui that's impossible only one guy can even
compete against him what's up with this guy he's using a martial art I've never seen before
go away stay put
who is this guy the blow didn't even stun him it's not just that he's strong or a good fighter
there's something else about him impressive you actually managed to land a hit this isn't the time
for compliments we have something to protect what's this you're walking away deal with them the two who
are hiding as well where are you going underground we've got orders the fight's over you two can come
out now looks like we've been found out what's he in such a hurry to get underground for it's obvious
isn't it he went to protect our water supply water yeah what else isn't that why you came to steal from
us we just got here we certainly haven't had time to plan a robbery really far away we don't know
the first thing about you or your country we didn't come to steal anything from you how cool what is that
creature some kind of mutant maybe it talks and everything kazuki stay away from an eclectic group
what do we do with them yuto kamu he was vague he just said to deal with them clearly he doesn't think
it's necessary to do away with them if he did then I'm sure he would have finished them off personally
I think you're right about that kakyo he doesn't hold anything back when it comes to protecting the
underground system well in that case I think we should take care of them without any more fighting
I agree so come on let's go the huge power I sensed is coming from the same direction the other guy went
if Moken is right about that we can't move on without investigating a little more first
um excuse me could you wait a moment please allow us to introduce ourselves this boy here is
shower on and my name is phi and this is gerger burger it's kirogane shower on's going to be in a
lot of pain with that arrow through his leg would you help us treat his wound we don't like to waste
our medicine but we owe him something come we shot the boy even though he isn't a thief we should help
him our resources are limited so I don't know how much help we can be but we'll try come with me
kakyo if kakyo says it'll be all right I'm with him we appreciate it fine but if you stay you work
kurupu will be more than happy to help with that since when were you in charge
this should buy us some time at least I just hope it's enough so do I
sorry about this and try not to get yourself shot through next time
hey it's kusanagi welcome back thanks
yet another patient for the infirmary it's okay it's not one of ours what happened are you hurt
no little one still good as new
are these the only people left in the city
wake up
do you mean me yes you have to wake up soon
acid rain has been falling here for 15 years now our rivers our ponds and our lakes none of the
groundwater we have is suitable for drinking anymore there used to be plenty of facilities
available for water filtration but even they haven't worked properly since the rain started falling
how have you survived this long here in Tokyo we have an underground water source that we've been
able to draw from you've seen the damage the acid rain has done to the buildings just think of what
it's done to the earth's surface the water's underground but it still has to be protected from
what's going on up here when we first came here I noticed how remarkably well preserved this building
is compared to the others in the area that's what makes the water so important it's still drinkable
the water here and in the tower
in the tower the only other place with good water only that building and this one survived
we're fighting with the people who live there with water being so scarce I guess it kind of makes sense
it hasn't always been like this until recently there were other buildings that were still standing
but now they've all crumbled so the tower and this city hall are the only ones left
and they haven't changed much in all these years so that's why you're upset water is really important
in this country I wouldn't exactly call it a country not many people are left only the 23 central wards
are still populated it's more of a ravaged city now than a country so welcome to Tokyo but what's left of it
how much longer do I have to stay in this place
I'm glad they gave us a room to sleep in
this is a tragic country princess I hope you don't wake until we move to the next one
there's nothing here you need to see
it feels like shower on's got a fever
I'll stay awake and look after them you can go ahead and sleep
hey now if you don't answer me I'm going to start feeling like a freak who talks to himself
and that wouldn't be very nice now would it
you answer something first
right what
why'd you use magic to help us escape
you've been near death before since we started traveling
but even then you never once used your power
you told us the reason for it
someone back in the country you're from is after you
and if you use magic he might be able to track you more easily
so you keep running from world to world without using magic
very impressive kurapu that's an excellent memory you have
come on now talk to me this is getting lonely
I don't care why you ran away from your home world
for all I know you're running scared because you're a wanted fugitive
it makes no difference to me one way or the other
and I wouldn't expect it to
because that is exactly the way you want it
you maintain your distance
you act frivolous and flippant all the time so no one will get close to you
but take a good look at yourself now
worrying about Shaoran's fever
trying to protect the princess from the misery of this country
and using magic to help us
I've told you before I'm not going to die
what you mean is you won't die for your own sake
but for someone else it's a totally different story
you didn't have to intervene back there
but we would have been killed if you hadn't
the library watchdogs would have torn us apart
and so you did what you promised yourself you weren't going to do
and now whether you like it or not Fi
you're involved
don't you see
the people close to me tend to get hurt
that's all I've ever wanted to prevent
could we talk to you for a minute
ah
Kurgi would be happy to talk to you guys
don't think I'm going to forget about our conversation
that hurts Kurgs
I told you
I don't care one way or the other
lovely
guess that means our conversation is finished
what I meant is that your past doesn't concern me
but the present
that is something I suggest you figure out
they're sleeping
we can talk outside
fine
my present
that's the hard part
where am I
am I
under water
you can't stay here
open your eyes
wake up
before you're trapped in your dream
you're wounded
are you sure that you're going to be all right
yeah
anyone who stays with us must do his part
and that's just the way it has to be
we don't have any food to spare for idle visitors
thanks
odd
I thought the big guy would have volunteered to come along for the hunt
he wanted to but I asked him to stay
the girl who's with us still isn't well
it worries me
she shouldn't be left alone
not in her state
Sharon and I came so he could stay behind with her
Kirk, he's babysitting
I'm gonna kill him
at least the rain stopped for now
keep your guard up
it's here
what is it?
nice aim stranger
it just so happens I've used this weapon once or twice before
what is that?
a friendly neighborhood mutant
it's poisonous but some parts are safe enough to eat
someone said that Mokuna was a mutant yesterday
does that mean the Mokuna's gonna be
oh you do look delicious
that's amazing
wow
are you okay?
fine, you?
your leg
oh, it's alright, thank you
nice catch, you bagged yourself a pretty big one, huh?
do you know who these guys are?
they're from the group in the tower
what was that?
the guys you told us you were fighting against?
yeah
as you can imagine
their leader and Kamui don't really get along
you're in a bad mood today
wonder why that is
seeing your face has that effect on me
he's right
they don't like each other much, huh?
looks like you're hunting some big game
I mean, food's necessary, of course
but it isn't as important a resource as water
then again
you'd know that
wouldn't you?
wow, you're moving slower than usual
are you injured or something?
probably from when he fought Kurupu
he really went flying
that was rather impolite, Fuma
I feel terrible
hey, Fuma
we got a message from the tower
we're being attacked by another ward
we keep fooling around
and they're gonna get their hands on our water
I guess we'd better go
I'm sure we'll meet again
see you later
that was entertaining
that Fuma guy knows how to fight
he's really strong
you've got that right
he's the only person in Tokyo
who can give Kamui a run for his money in a fight
Kamui and Fuma must be the top dogs in this city
is that how it's always been?
no, it was different before
Kamui's story has a lot in common with yours
it's been about two years now
his arrival in Tokyo was very sudden
he appeared in City Hall
the building we live in
without warning
at first we were convinced
he'd come to steal our water
he was a bit out of it at the time
confused or disoriented somehow
disoriented?
I think Kazuki put it best
he said that Kamui had the look of a child
who'd lost his way
then he looked at the water and spoke
I'm staying
I'll protect it
and so from that point on
Kamui has become a permanent part of your lives here?
that's right
Kakyo said something
he thinks you and Kamui are similar
and that you're both searching single-mindedly for something
he's right
there's something I have to find
no matter what
he's waking up
she's right
Shaoran.
Why are you here?
Why are you talking to me?
You've been sleeping.
But you have to wake up now.
I can't.
I don't know how.
Wake up.
Someone you care about needs you.
Hey.
Princess, wake up.
Oh no.
She isn't breathing.
I sense the weather.
It's really strong.
Can't you tell me where it's coming from, Hokunar?
It's back there.
Under the building where the others are.
Under City Hall.
Careful, Fi.
Don't you see? Shaoran isn't after your water.
He's looking for something Sakura needs.
Sakura.
It's something very important for someone very important to me.
We should have realized that the seal wouldn't hold you forever.
You're going, aren't you?
I won't stop you.
But you don't have the power to travel through dimensions.
Lucky for you, I can help.
But I can only do this once.
Why would you do this?
Why, you ask?
Because the dream must end.
I'll find a doctor.
If a doctor would even know what to do.
This isn't something medicine can help.
You came from more than a different world.
It was an entirely different dimension.
You're here at last.
I'll find another.
Thank you.